FRAN GARCIA / Drupal web developer

https://www.fjgarlin.com

I am an experienced Drupal web developer, specialised in long term maintenance of Drupal projects. I am really enthusiastic about what I do and enjoy solving problems, debugging and fixing code. I also enjoy helping and mentoring other people.

EXPERIENCE

Amazee Labs (2017-current) - Global Maintenance Team, Remote Senior Drupal Web Developer & Team Lead Maintenance & Support - Drupal 6 to 9, React, Gatsby, GraphQL... Active Drupal contributions and speaker at conferences

IE Design Consultancy (2012-2017) - Birmingham, UK
Drupal Web Developer & Team Leader & Technical Manager
Drupal 6 to 8, Bootstrap, SASS...
Drupal certification

Friend MTS (2011-2012) - Birmingham, UK Web Developer Zend Framework, Smarty...

Alia Multimedia (2010-2011) - Granada, Spain Junior Web Developer *PHP, Smarty...*

Escuela Arte Granada (2007-2010) - Granada, Spain IT Teacher (Junior college level)

Programming, Databases, Networking...

EDUCATION

Computer Science BSc (2003-2006) - University of Granada *First Class Honours*

Teaching certificate (2007) - University of Granada

LANGUAGES

English and **Spanish** (native)